Shubham Sharma

Software Engineer

As a frontend developer with 2+ years of experience, I have a proven track record of building visually appealing websites using ReactJS, Redux, HTML-CSS, JavaScript. Additionally, I have experience in working with Angular framework and also have a strong understanding of GIT version control and have experience working in Agile environments, utilizing Scrum to improve project workflows and increase efficiency.

\times	shubhr0813@gmail.com
-	7830797962
0	Raipur C.G
B	shubhsportfolio.netlify.app
in	linkedin.com/in/shubhs18
0	github.com/shubhshar

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Tech Mahindra 08/2021 - 04/2023

Pune, India

 Build components of website from scratch using ReactJS. Working with technologies like Redux, ES6, HTML5 and CSS3, REST-API GIT, Oracle SQL. Worked to optimize the website performance and responsiveness with good understanding of CSS based design and cross-browser compatibility.

Software Engineer Trainee

ANR Software

03/2021 - 07/2021

Noida, India

 Developed changes required in web applications using HTML-CSS and JavaScript. Deployed the changes and doing the Unit Testing. Developed & integrated the front-end with back-end aspects of the web application with good understanding of web standards,

EDUCATION

B. Tech (Computer Science)

Dr. APJ Abdul Kalam Technical University

07/2016 - 01/2021

7.2 GPA

SKILLS

ReactJS Redux HTML5 CSS

Javascript Oracle SQL Git Bootstrap

PROJECTS

Onward Billing Portal (Client- British Telecom)

- Developed a React based application to show data created by legacy application running on server to different users and process the invoices further.
- Technology used: HTML/CSS, React, Redux, Bootstrap, SQL, RestAPI, Java (Spring)

Gaztec Rate Upload (Client- British Telecom)

- Developed the web pages from scratch and integrated the APIs in the web application.
- Technology used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Spring, OracleSQL., Shell-Script.

Gaztec Network Mediation (Client- British Telecom)

- Developed lookups based on criteria provided by designer and deploy the jar on server and process the NAR accordingly.
- Technology Used: Java, SQL, Shell script, UNIX commands.

E-Restaurant management (Anr Software)

- Developed the responsive web pages according to the client requirements. Added responsiveness to the pages for seamless user experience.
- Technology used: HTML/CSS, JavaScript, OracleSQL.

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency